export const onlineTestsInfo = [
  {
    title: 'IIT JEE - Main',
    type: 'Practise Test',
    description: 'Mock Test - Paper I',
    questions: '40',
    marks: '60',
    time: '60',
    cost: 'free'
  },
  {
    title: 'GRE',
    type: 'Adaptive Test',
    description: 'Mock Test - Paper II',
    questions: '40',
    marks: '60',
    time: '60',
    cost: 'free'
  },
  {
    title: 'SSC',
    type: 'Practise Test',
    description: 'Tier-II',
    questions: '60',
    marks: '90',
    time: '90',
    cost: '100'
  },
  {
    title: 'IIT JEE - Advance',
    type: 'Practise Test',
    description: 'Mock Test - Paper I',
    questions: '30',
    marks: '30',
    time: '45',
    cost: '100'
  },
  {
    title: 'CAT',
    type: 'Adaptive Test',
    description: 'Mock Test - Paper I',
    questions: '60',
    marks: '60',
    time: '90',
    cost: 'free'
  }
];

export const testQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'The resolutions on Fundamental Rights and National Economic Policy were passed in which of the following sessions of the Indian National Congress?',
    options : [
      {
        num: 1,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Belgaum,1934'
      },
      {
        num: 1,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Lahore,1929'
      },
      {
        num: 1,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Karachi,1931'
      },
      {
        num: 1,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Faizpur,1936'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Karachi,1931'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who founded the Ramakrishna Mission in 1896 to carry on humanitarian relief and social work?',
    options : [
      {
        num: 2,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Ramakrishna Paramahansa'
      },
      {
        num: 2,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Swami Dayananda Saraswati'
      },
      {
        num: 2,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Swami Vivekananda'
      },
      {
        num: 2,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Blavatsky and Olcott'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Swami Vivekananda'
  },
  {

    question: 'Which among the following Viceroys was associated with the ‘Ilbert Bill Controversy’?',
    options : [
      {
        num: 3,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Lord Curzon'
      },
      {
        num: 3,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Lord Lytton'
      },
      {
        num: 3,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Lord Ripon'
      },
      {
        num: 3,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Lord Hardinge'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lord Ripon'
  },
  {
    question: 'Subhash Chandra Bose was re-elected the President of INC at the Tripuri Session in 1939 by defeating Gandhiji’s candidate :',
    options : [
      {
        num: 4,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Dr. Rajendra Prasad'
      },
      {
        num: 4,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'J.B.Kriplani'
      },
      {
        num: 4,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Nellie Sengupta'
      },
      {
        num: 4,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Pattabhi Sitaramaiyya'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pattabhi Sitaramaiyya'
  },
  {
    question: 'The pioneer of Communism in India was:',
    options : [
      {
        num: 5,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'S.A.Dange'
      },
      {
        num: 5,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'M.R.Jayakar'
      },
      {
        num: 5,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'M.N.Roy'
      },
      {
        num: 5,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Nalin Gupta'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'M.N.Roy'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following was the most controversial measure of Lord Mountbatten?',
    options : [
      {
        num: 6,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Partitioning of Punjab and Bengal'
      },
      {
        num: 6,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Holding of a referendum in the North West Frontier Province (NWFP)'
      },
      {
        num: 6,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Setting up of an Executive Council comprising of Indians alone'
      },
      {
        num: 6,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Advancing the date of transfer of power from June 1948 to August 15,1947'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Advancing the date of transfer of power from June 1948 to August 15,1947'
  },
  {
    question: 'Both the processes of transfer of power and the partition of India were hurried through in ____ days.',
    options : [
      {
        num: 7,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: '68'
      },
      {
        num: 7,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: '70'
      },
      {
        num: 7,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: '72'
      },
      {
        num: 7,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: '85'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: '72'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Swaraj Party was divided into factions after the death of C.R.Das and its ‘Responsivists’ faction worked for/by:',
    options : [
      {
        num: 8,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Safeguarding the hindu interests by cooperating with the British Government.'
      },
      {
        num: 8,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Creating obstacles in legislative process by acting as dissenters.'
      },
      {
        num: 8,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Cooperating with the No-Changers of the Congress in the favour of constructive programme of Gandhi.'
      },
      {
        num: 8,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Maintaining a separate identity of the Party within the Congress.'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Safeguarding the hindu interests by cooperating with the British Government'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which among the following great revolutionaries was the brain behind the ‘Chittagong Armoury Raid’?',
    options : [
      {
        num: 9,
        optName: 'A',
        opt: 'Ganesh Ghosh'
      },
      {
        num: 9,
        optName: 'B',
        opt: 'Chandrashekhar Azad'
      },
      {
        num: 9,
        optName: 'C',
        opt: 'Surya Sen'
      },
      {
        num: 9,
        optName: 'D',
        opt: 'Lala Hardayal'
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Surya Sen'
  },
  {

  question: 'Who among the following was popularly known as the ‘Frontier Gandhi’?',
  options : [
    {
      num: 10,
      optName: 'A',
      opt: 'Hasrat Mohani'
    },
    {
      num: 10,
      optName: 'B',
      opt: 'Maulana Abul Kalam Azad'
    },
    {
      num: 10,
      optName: 'C',
      opt: 'Khan Abdul Ghaffar Khan'
    },
    {
      num: 10,
      optName: 'D',
      opt: 'Iqbal Khan'
    },
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Khan Abdul Ghaffar Khan'
},
]
